slideworld.org 2009-04-01

# slide world(search online Powerpoint Presentation,SlideShow,Featured Slides,Blog,Submit Slides)

### Privacy Policy

At Slideworld we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Slideworld's services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

**Scope**

**** This notice offers highlights of the full Slideworld Privacy Policy which describes in detail the privacy practices that apply to Slideworld's features.

**Personal information and other data we collect**

Slideworld collects personal information when you register for a Slideworld service or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other Slideworld services or third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.

Slideworld uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use Slideworld services in order to improve the quality of our services.

Slideworld's servers automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request.

**Uses**

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.

We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve Slideworld technologies and services.

We may share with third parties outside of Slideworld.

When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

Slideworld processes personal information on our servers in the  United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country.

**Your choices**

We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible. You can find more information about your choices in the privacy notices or FAQs for specific services.

You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result.

     1\. We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible.

**More information**

For more information about our privacy practices, go to the full privacy policy. If you have additional questions regarding your privacy and Slideworld, please contact us _._ Please note that we will not respond to inquiries not related to Slideworld's Privacy Policy
